okay this one keeps coming up I don't
even talk about it I specialist go and
talk about it in public but it keeps
coming up so I think if I don't release
it then more won't come or it's needed
it's needed in the world and that's a
website slash app for pedophiles
and I think that they're very
villainized our society and those that
act on their urges are rightfully
punished but that we don't have any way
for them to be themselves without
hurting children is ridiculous and so
the more we can come together as a
society and solve that problem
we'll make children safer and that's
always way less likely to commit the
crime that we all seem to hate them for
and so that these people exist in our
society and how do we as a society best
allow them to exist